<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<RelativeLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context="com.example.ash.smartamravati.activity.user.dashboard.AmravatiCity.Introduction">
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent">
        <RelativeLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent">



            <TextView
                android:id="@+id/textView8"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="50dp"
                android:layout_gravity="center"
                android:layout_marginBottom="8dp"
                android:layout_marginEnd="8dp"
                android:layout_marginStart="8dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="8dp"
                android:fontFamily="sans-serif-condensed"
                android:text="Amravati City History"
                android:textColor="@color/colorPrimary"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textSize="35dp"
                android:textStyle="bold"
                app:layout_constraintBottom_toBottomOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintEnd_toEndOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintStart_toStartOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintTop_toTopOf="parent"
                app:layout_constraintVertical_bias="0.017" />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
                android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
                android:layout_marginTop="70dp"
                android:text=" \n     The ancient name of Amravati is 'Udumbravati', in prakrut, 'Umbravati'. \nThe variant 'Amravati' is the presently accepted name. It is said that Amravati is named for its ancient Ambadevi temple. A mention of Amravati can be found on a stone inscription on the base of the marble statue of God Adinath (Jain God) Rhishabhnath. The statues date back to the year 1097. Govind Maha Prabhu visited Amravati in the 13th century, when Wardha was under the rule of Deogiri's Hindu King (Yadava dynasty). In the 14th century, there was drought and famine in Amravati, so people abandoned Amravati and left for Gujrat and Malwa. Though some locals returned after several years, this resulted in a scanty population. In the 16th century, Magar Aurangpura (today, 'Sabanpura') was alloted for a Jama Masjid by Mughal Aurangzeb. This indicates the existence of a Muslim population. In 1722, Chhattrapati Shahu presented Amravati and Badnera to Shri Ranoji Bhosle; eventually Amravati was known as Bhosle ki Amravati. The city was reconstructed and developed by Ranoji Bhosle after the treaty of Devgaon and Anjangaon Surji and victory over Gavilgad (Fort of Chikhaldara). The British general and author Wellesly camped in Amravati, the place is still known as the 'camp', by Amravati people. Amravati city was founded towards the end of the 18th century. The Union state of Nijam and Bosale ruled Amravati. They appointed a revenue officer but neglected defence. The Gavilgad fort was conquered by the British on 15 December 1803. Under to the Deogaon treaty, Warhad was presented as a token of the friendship to the Nijam. \n\n.
"
                android:textAlignment="center"
                android:textSize="20dp"
                android:textStyle="italic" />

        </RelativeLayout>



    </ScrollView>

</RelativeLayout>
